vishal salunke

04/02/1991 • Indian • salunkevishal05@gmail.com • +917798424352

Address

D-303 , Poorva residency , pimple Saudagar Pune 411027 India

Profile

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the marketing and advertising industry. Skilled in Node js, Angular JS, React, Web Development, Amazon Web Services (AWS), Jekyll. Strong engineering professional graduated from University of Pune.

Experience

Carpro systems • Pune • India

Software Developer

03/2016 - 10/2017

- Coding, testing and fixing programming errors.
- · Communication with clients.
- Conduct training for new developers. Analyzing customer requirements.
- Full stack development of various modules.

Quinstreet - Pune - India

Software Developer

11/2017 – present

- Design and development of various websites.
- Support and development of new functionality for already existing projects.
- Analysis of business requirement.
- Conducting job interviews.
- Created responsive websites from scratch.

Education

Modern college of engineering, pune university pune India

Bachelor of engineering in information technology

06/2010 - 06/2015

Skills

Programming skills

Node js ■■■□

React

AngularJs ■■■□

Aws Redshift ■■□□

Aws lamda ■■□□□

Sql ■■□□□

API ••••

Web Development ■■■□

HTML ====

CSS ■■■□□

Javascript ■■■□□

Jekyll ■■■□□

Languages

English ■■■□

Hobbies

Exploring distant lands • Capturing moments • Feeling the music • Every kind of sport